Finding aid to the James Parker records, 1924-2005 Archives.Parker.1
The Metropolitan Museum of Art Archives
- Series I. Research, 1912-1997, n.d.; 31.0 Linear feet (72 boxes, 839 folders)
  - Subseries I.A. Card File, 1922-1933, 1943-1950, 1957-1996, n.d.; 25.0 Linear feet (60 boxes, 722 folders)
    - Textiles. G - U. (Box 53, Folder 9)
      Note: Includes German. Italian. Peruvian. Portuguese. Russian. U.S.A.
    - Tôle. (Box 53, Folder 10)
      See also: Series I. Research / Subseries I.A. Card File / f. Enamels.
    - Topography and descriptive. Austrian. (Box 54, Folder 1)
      Note: Includes information on specific houses, castles, manors, etc., their furnishings, biographies of owners and their families, as well as the history of specific furniture items. The locations most cited are noted, but are in no way a complete representation of contents. Includes Guidebooks. Churches. Palaces and castles. A - Z. Vienna (general, views of, guidebooks, palaces).
    - Topography and descriptive. Belgian. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Topography and descriptive. C. (Box 54, Folder 3)
      Note: Includes Chinese. Czechoslovakian. Contains correspondence from F.J.B. Watson to Jayne Wrightsman (1982).
    - Topography and descriptive. D. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Topography and descriptive. English. (Box 54, Folder 5)
      Note: Includes Essex. Kent. London. Middlesex. Northumberland. Surrey. Yorkshire. Churches. Houses. National Trust. Contains correspondence from P.A. Bezodis, Greater London Council (1966).
    - Topography and descriptive. English (A). (Box 54, Folder 6)
      Note: Includes Audley End. Cites - Adelphi, Althorp, Anglesey Abbey, Apsley House, Arbury Hall, Arlington Street, Avebury Manor, Aynhoe Park. Contains correspondence from William C. McKemie, Agecroft Association (1978) and between James Biddle, Victoria and Albert Museum and Jack R. McGregor, M.M.A. (1960).
    - Topography and descriptive. English (B - Bl). (Box 54, Folder 7)
      Note: Includes Blenheim. Cites - Badminton House, Balls Park, Balmoral, Bath, Belmont Park, Belton House, Belvoir Castle, Berkeley Square, Berrington Hall, Bisterne, Blair.
    - Topography and descriptive. English (Bo - Bu). (Box 54, Folder 8)
      Note: Includes Brighton. Buckingham. Cites - Boughton House, Bourne Park, Bowood, Bramshill Park, Bretby, Brighton Pavilion, Broadlands, Brocket Hall, Browsholme Hall, Buckingham Palace, Burghley House, Burton Constable. Contains correspondence from Victoria and Albert Museum (signature of writer illegible) to John Goldsmith Phillips, M.M.A. (1959).
    - Topography and descriptive. English (Ca). (Box 54, Folder 9)
      Note: Includes Carlton House (desks). Cites - Cadland, Cambridge, Canons Ashby, Carlisle House, Carrington House, Cassiobury Park, Castle Howard.
    - Topography and descriptive. English (Ch - C). (Box 54, Folder 10)
      Note: Includes Croome Court. Cites - Charlecote Park, Charleston House, Chatsworth, Chesterfield House, Chiswick House, Clandon, Claremont, Clarence House, Claverton Manor, Claydon, Clumber Park, Combe Abbey, Corsham Court. Contains correspondence to William Redford (1976), with Roy Strong, Victoria and Albert Museum (1978), between Neil Sellin and William Rieder, M.M.A. (1978) and an M.M.A. memorandum from William Rieder to Olga Raggio (1978).
    - Topography and descriptive. English (D). (Box 54, Folder 11)
      Note: Cites - Daylesford House, Deene Park, Denham Place, Denne Park, Denton Park, Derby House, Devonshire House, Ditchley, Ditton, Dodington, Dorchester House, Dorest, Dover, Drayton, Dudley House, Dyrham Park.
    - Topography and descriptive. English (E). (Box 54, Folder 12)
      Note: Cites - Eaton Hall, Elton Hall, Euston Hall.
    - Topography and descriptive. English (F). (Box 54, Folder 13)
      Note: Cites - Felbrigg Hall, Firle Place, Fonthill Abbey, Frogmore House.
    - Topography and descriptive. English (G). (Box 55, Folder 1)
      Note: Cites - Goodwood House, Gorhambury, Grange, Grimsthorpe Castle, Grosvenor House. Contains correspondence from Amyas Phillips, Phillips of Hitchin Ltd. to John Goldsmith Phillips, M.M.A. (1957).
    - Topography and descriptive. English (H). (Box 55, Folder 2)
      Note: Cites - Hackwood, Ham House, Hamilton Palace, Hampton Court Palace, Hardwick Hall, Harewood House, Haseley Court, Hatfield House, Heveningham Hall, Hever Castle, Hinton House, Holkham Hall, Holland House, Holme Lacy, Hornby Castle, Houghton Hall. Contains correspondence from Earl Reiss, Douglas Elliman Knight Frank Inc. to William Macomber, M.M.A. (1984), from Clarendon Court (signature of writer illegible) (1976), from Edward Benjamin, E.H. Benjamin to Joseph Breck, M.M.A. (1931) and from F.A.J. Emery-Wallis, Hursley Park, Hampshire (1988).
    - Topography and descriptive. English (I - K). (Box 55, Folder 3)
      Note: Cites - Ickworth Park, Inveraray Castle, Kedleston, Kempshott House, Kensington Palace, Kenwood, Kew, Kimbolton Castle, Kingston Lacy, Kirtlington Park, Knole.
    - Topography and descriptive. English (L). (Box 55, Folder 4)
      Note: Includes Lansdowne House. Cites - Langley, Linton, Londonderry House, Longford Castle, Longleat House, Lowther Castle, Luton Hoo.
    - Topography and descriptive. English (M). (Box 55, Folder 5)
      Note: Cites - Mansion House, Marble Hill, Marlborough House, Melbury House, Mentmore, Mersham- Le- Hatch, Milton, Montagu House, Moor Park. Contains correspondence with E.B. Everett, The Old Parsonage Hinxton (1966) and from Nancy Idaka, Yale University Art Gallery (1977).
    - Topography and descriptive. English (N - O). (Box 55, Folder 6)
      Note: Includes Norfolk. Cites - Newby Hall, Newstead, Nonsuch Palace, Northumberland House, Nostell Priory, Ockwells Manor, Osterley Park, Oxford.
    - Topography and descriptive. English (P - R). (Box 55, Folder 7)
      Note: Cites - Pantheon, Parham, Pencarrow, Petworth House, Pineapple as ornament, Platt Hall, Polesden Lacey, Powderham Castle, Powis Castle, Preston Manor, Queen's House, Ragley, Ranelagh, Raynham Hall, Rousham.
    - Topography and descriptive. English (S). (Box 55, Folder 8)
      Note: Cites - Saint Dustan's Villa, Saint Giles' House, Saint James's Palace, Saint Paul's Cathedral, Saltram, Scarisbrick, Sezincote, Shardeloes, Shugborough, Somerley, Somerset House, Southill, Spencer House, Squerryes Court, Stafford House, Stonor Park, Stourhead, Stowe, Stratfield Saye, Strawberry Hill, Streatlam Castle, Sudbury, Sutton Place, Syon House. Contains correspondence from Richard F. Sunilows (1977).
    - Topography and descriptive. English (T - V). (Box 55, Folder 9)
      Note: Cites - Temple Newsam, Tunbridge, Uppark, Vauxhall, Vyne.
    - Topography and descriptive. English (W - Y). (Box 55, Folder 10)
      Note: Includes Windsor Castle. Woburn Abbey. Cites - Waddesdon Manor, Wanstead House, Warwick Castle, Wentworth Woodhouse, Westminster Abbey, Weston Park, Wilton House, Wimpole Hall, York. Contains correspondence from Peter N. Sheridan to Jane Wayward, The Cloisters (1990) and from Martha McKelvie (1970).
    - Topography and descriptive. Finnish. (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Topography and descriptive. French. (Box 56, Folder 1)
      Note: Includes Châteaux (general).
    - Topography and descriptive. French (A). (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Topography and descriptive. French (B). (Box 56, Folder 3)
      Note: Includes Bagatelle. Bellevue. Bordeaux. Palais Bourbon Contains correspondence from Pierre Verlet (1985)
    - Topography and descriptive. French (C - Ch). (Box 56, Folder 4)
      Note: Includes Chanteloup. Chantilly. Choisy. Contains correspondence from Gillian Wilson, J. Paul Getty Museum (1980).
    - Topography and descriptive. French (Ci - Cr). (Box 56, Folder 5)
      Note: Includes Compiegne. Concorde (Place de la). Contains correspondence from Jean-Marie Moulin, Ministère de la Culture et de l'Environnement (1978), Gillian Wilson, J. Paul Getty Museum (1973) and Alan Hartman (1968).
    - Topography and descriptive. French (D - E). (Box 56, Folder 6)
      Note: Includes Elysée.
    - Topography and descriptive. French (F). (Box 56, Folder 7)
      Note: Includes Fontainebleau.
    - Topography and descriptive. French (G - H). (Box 56, Folder 8)
      Note: Contains correspondence to Abbie Gail Weiser (1980) and from Preston Remington, M.M.A. to Paul M. Byk, Arnold Seligmann, Rey and Co., Inc. (1932).
    - Topography and descriptive. French (I - K). Box 56, Folder 9 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Topography and descriptive. French (L). (Box 56, Folder 10)
      Note: Includes Lauzun (Hôtel). Louveciennes. Louvre. Contains correspondence from Robert Samuels, Jr., French and Company, Inc. (1961), A. Theodore Dell (1966) and to Victor Moritz (1982).
    - Topography and descriptive. French (M - Me). (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Note: Includes Malmaison. Marly. Menus-Plaisirs. Contains correspondence from Betsy Jean Rosasco to Penelope Hunter (1972).
    - Topography and descriptive. French (Mi - Mu). (Box 57, Folder 2)
      Note: Contains correspondence with Heather L. Hahn (1989) and from Richard Faber (1986).
    - Topography and descriptive. French (N - O). (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Topography and descriptive. French (P). (Box 57, Folder 4)
      Note: Includes Palais Royal. Paris. Environs de Paris.
    - Topography and descriptive. French (Q - R). [Contains correspondence from André Cariou to Jacob Bean, M.M.A. (1986) and from Edith A. Standen, M.M.A. (1971).] Box 57, Folder 5 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Topography and descriptive. French (S - Sa). (Box 57, Folder 6)
      Note: Includes Saint Cloud (general, ceramics, furniture, exterior views, interiors and floor plans, gilt bronze, textiles). Saint Hubert. Contains correspondence from A. Schmitz, Domaine National de Saint-Cloud (1976).
    - Topography and descriptive. French (Sc - Su). (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Topography and descriptive. French (T - Tr). (Box 57, Folder 8)
      Note: Includes Trianon (grand). Petit Trianon (porcelain). Contains correspondence from Annie Cohen-Solal, Ambassade de France Cultural Counsellor to Philippe de Montebello (1991).
    - Topography and descriptive. French (Tu). (Box 57, Folder 9)
      Note: Includes Tuileries (exterior, general, furniture marks, furniture inventories, textiles, floor plans, gardens, 17th century, Napoleon I, 1830-1870). Contains correspondence from P.G. Leperpier (1983).
    - Topography and descriptive. French (U - Verr). (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Topography and descriptive. French (Vers - W). (Box 58, Folder 1)
      Note: Includes Versailles (chapel, furniture, gardens, hameau, interiors, opera, orangerie, paintings, plans, sculptures). Contains 1 slide.
    - Topography and descriptive. German. (Box 58, Folder 2)
      Note: Includes A - Z. Bavaria. Berlin. Cologne. Dresden. Frankfurt. Hamburg. Mainz. Munich. Wurzburg. Contains 1 booklet containing 12 photos of Schloss Pillnitz (1977).
    - Topography and descriptive. H - In. (Box 58, Folder 3)
      Note: Includes Hungarian. Indian.
    - Topography and descriptive. Irish. (Box 58, Folder 4)
      Note: Includes Dublin. A - Z.
    - Topography and descriptive. Italian (A - Fe). (Box 58, Folder 5)
      Note: Includes A - Z. Bologna. Ferrara.
    - Topography and descriptive. Italian (Fl). (Box 58, Folder 6)
      Note: Includes Florence (Bonapartes in, churches, palaces and villas, Tuscany).
    - Topography and descriptive. Italian (G - M). (Box 58, Folder 7)
      Note: Includes Genoa (palaces and villas. Lucca. Mantua. Milan.
    - Topography and descriptive. Italian (N). (Box 58, Folder 8)
      Note: Includes Naples (churches, Caserta near).
    - Topography and descriptive. Italian (P). (Box 58, Folder 9)
      Note: Includes Padua. Parma.
    - Topography and descriptive. Italian (R). (Box 58, Folder 10)
      Note: Includes Rome (architecture, churches, fountains, guidebooks, palaces (general), palaces (by name), piazza, plans of, villas, views of). Contains correspondence from Olga Raggio, M.M.A. (1971).
    - Topography and descriptive. Italian (S - Va). (Box 58, Folder 11)
      Note: Includes Sicily. Turin and Piedmont (Agnelli Villa, Racconigi). Urbino. Varese. Contains correspondence from Henry Sorensen (1980).
    - Topography and descriptive. Italian (Ve - Vi). (Box 58, Folder 12)
      Note: Includes Venice (architecture, churches, palaces, Veneto and villas). Verona. Vicenza.
    - Topography and descriptive. L - M. (Box 58, Folder 13)
      Note: Includes Liechtenstein. Maltese.
    - Topography and descriptive. Polish. (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Topography and descriptive. Portuguese. (Box 58, Folder 15)
      Note: Contains correspondence to Ed Nelson (1972).
    - Topography and descriptive. Russian. (Box 59, Folder 1)
      Note: Includes French in. Palaces and cities. People [Charles Cameron]. Sculpture.
    - Topography and descriptive. Scottish. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Topography and descriptive. Spanish. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Topography and descriptive. Sw. (Box 59, Folder 4)
      Note: Includes Swedish. Swiss.
    - Topography and descriptive. Turkish. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Topography and descriptive. U.S.A. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Topography and descriptive. W - Y. (Box 59, Folder 7)
      Note: Includes Welsh. Yugoslavian.
    - Tour, grand. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Wallpaper. (Box 59, Folder 9)
      Note: Includes Chinese. English. French (17th - 19th centuries). Italian. Spanish. U.S.A. Contains 2 slides and correspondence from Jack R. McGregor, M.H. de Young Memorial Museum (1968).
    - Waxes. (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Woodwork and interiors. A - D. (Box 59, Folder 11)
      Note: Includes Austrian. Belgian. Czechoslovakian. Danish. Dutch (Bathrooms). Contains correspondence from Theodore J. Svalgard, Theo. J. Svalgård, Inc. to Gazetten Construction Inc. (1987).
    - Woodwork and interiors. English (1 of 5). (Box 59, Folder 12)
      Note: Includes A - Z craftsmen. Contains correspondence between Preston Remington, M.M.A. and Maggs Bros., London (1933).
    - Woodwork and interiors. English (2 of 5). (Box 59, Folder 13)
      Note: Includes 16th - 19th centuries. Contains correspondence from Peter N. Sheridan to Jane Wayward, The Cloisters (1990).
    - Woodwork and interiors. English (3 of 5). (Box 59, Folder 14)
      Note: Includes Bathrooms. Brackets (wall). Ceilings. Colors and gilding. Doors.
    - Woodwork and interiors. English (4 of 5). (Box 59, Folder 15)
      Note: Includes Floors. Marbleizing and graining. Overdoors and overmantels. Plaster and composition. Shop fronts. Staircases.
    - Woodwork and interiors. English (5 of 5). (Box 59, Folder 16)
      Note: Includes Tent rooms. Venetian blinds. Wall decorations (fabrics and papers). Windows. Window decorations (blinds and curtains).
    - Woodwork and interiors. French (1 of 11). (Box 60, Folder 1)
      Note: Includes A - Z craftsmen. Contains correspondence to John Harris, Royal Institute of British Architects (1965). Contains 4 photographs.See also: Series I. Research / Subseries I.A. Card File / f. Painting. French.
    - Woodwork and interiors. French (2 of 11). (Box 60, Folder 2)
      Note: Includes 16th - 18th centuries.
    - Woodwork and interiors. French (3 of 11). (Box 60, Folder 3)
      Note: Includes Louis XIII. Louis XIV. Régence. Contains 1 photograph.
    - Woodwork and interiors. French (4 of 11). (Box 60, Folder 4)
      Note: Includes Louis XV. Louis XVI. Contains correspondence from Alan Hartman, Hartman Trading Corp. (1968).
    - Woodwork and interiors. French (5 of 11). (Box 60, Folder 5)
      Note: Includes Empire. 19th century. Pompeian style. 20th century.
    - Woodwork and interiors. French (6 of 11). (Box 60, Folder 6)
      Note: Includes Bathrooms.
    - Woodwork and interiors. French (7 of 11). (Box 60, Folder 7)
      Note: Includes Ceilings.
    - Woodwork and interiors. French (8 of 11). (Box 60, Folder 8)
      Note: Includes Colors and gilding or lack of.
    - Woodwork and interiors. French (9 of 11). (Box 60, Folder 9)
      Note: Includes Doors. Fabric-hung rooms.
    - Woodwork and interiors. French (10 of 11). (Box 60, Folder 10)
      Note: Includes Flooring (Louis XIV - Louis XVI).
    - Woodwork and interiors. French (11 of 11). (Box 60, Folder 11)
      Note: Includes Marbleizing and graining (Napoleon). Niches for beds. Overdoors. Shop fronts. Shutters. Staircases. Stuccos. Venetian blinds. Windows.
    - Woodwork and interiors. German. (Box 60, Folder 12)
      Note: Includes Bathrooms
    - Woodwork and interiors. I. (Box 60, Folder 13)
      Note: Includes Irish. Italian (bathrooms). Contains correspondence with Spence T. Brennan (1993).
    - Woodwork and interiors. P - U. (Box 60, Folder 14)
      Note: Includes Polish. Portuguese. Russian. Scottish. Silvering on wood. Spanish. Swedish. Swiss. U.S.A.
  - Subseries I.B. General, 1922-1924, 1930-1937, 1947-1997, n.d.; 2.5 Linear feet (6 boxes, 56 folders)
    This subseries is significantly smaller in scope than the “card file” subseries, although it is similar with regards to content. It represents a fraction of Parker’s original documentation, much of which was transferred to relevant departmental object files. Subjects are varied across the decorative arts field, and include makers, materials, techniques, exhibitions, locales, styles and authors. As is the case in the “card file” subseries, the majority of material is comprised of annotated examples of objects clipped or photocopied from auction catalogs, serials and monographs. Correspondence and memoranda, photographic materials, newsletters, and relevant research items contained in folders are noted. Some research materials are copies of original inventories and documents that date from the eighteenth and nineteenth centuries. Several unpublished manuscripts related to English furniture and interiors in the Museum’s collection and furniture maker B.V.R.B., by John Cornforth and Jean-Pierre Baroli, respectively, are noteworthy. Accession numbers are indicated when known. All materials within folders were filed as found, regardless of dated materials.
    The materials were removed from their original file folders and notebook binders and filed alphabetically by subject matter.
    - Adam, Robert., n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1)
      Note: Adam, Robert, 1728-1792. Contains 23 photographs and an inventory of drawings (1760-1781).
    - Bellevue, Château de., 1969, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 2)
      Note: Contains research materials pertaining to furniture owned by the Mesdames Tantes. Contains correspondence with Henry Sorensen.
    - Bérain, Jean., n.d. (Box 61, Folder 3)
      Note: Bérain, Jean, 1640-1711. Contains 17 photographs.
    - Bronze, gilt (1 of 2)., 1971, 1974-1975, 1979-1981, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      Note: Contains materials pertaining to the cleaning of and identifying marks on gilt-bronze, etc. Contains correspondence with Gillian Wilson (J. Paul Getty Museum), Douglas Dillon (M.M.A.), Henry Hawley (Cleveland Museum of Art), Sam R. Matthews, Michael Stürmer (Friedrich-Alexander Universität), Pierre Verlet, Peter Pröschel (Galerie Carroll), Lisa Taylor and David Revere McFadden (Cooper-Hewitt Museum) and Sarah Medlam (Bowes Museum). Contains 7 photographs.
    - Bronze, gilt (2 of 2)., 1870, 1924, 1931, 1937, 1950, 1953, 1956, 1963, 1969, 1974, 1977, 1980, 1982, 1985, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - B.V.R.B. (1 of 2)., 1960-1961, 1980, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 6)
      Note: Risenburgh, Bernard van, II (French ébéniste, after 1696-ca. 1766). Contains correspondence with Jean-Pierre Baroli and Henry Sorensen.
    - B.V.R.B. (2 of 2)., 1960 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      Note: Contains "Ébéniste B.V.R.B." by Jean-Pierre Baroli.
    - Cabinets (painted)., n.d. (Box 61, Folder 8)
      Note: Contains 3 photographs and 1 transparency.
    - Clocks. Louis XIV., 1989, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 9)
      Note: Contains correspondence from Barry L. Shifman, Indianapolis Museum of Art.
    - Clocks. Louis XV (1 of 2)., n.d. (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Clocks. Louis XV (2 of 2)., n.d. (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Clocks. Louis XVI (1 of 5)., n.d. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Clocks. Louis XVI (3 of 5)., n.d. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Clocks. Louis XVI (4 of 5)., 1991, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 3)
      Note: Contains correspondence from Jean-Marie van Isacker to William Rieder, M.M.A.
    - Clocks. Louis XVI (5 of 5)., 1983, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 4)
      Note: Contains correspondence with Anthony G. Victoria, Frederick P. Victoria and Son, Inc.
    - Clocks. Empire (1 of 4)., 1965, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 5)
      Note: Contains research materials inside a heavily annotated issue of The Connoisseur(January 1965).
    - Clocks. Empire (2 of 4)., n.d. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Clocks. Empire (3 of 4)., n.d. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Clocks. Empire (4 of 4)., n.d. (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Clocks. 19th century., n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Cooper Union Museum., 1959, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 2)
      Note: Cooper Union Museum for the Arts of Decoration. Contains 11 photographs.
    - Cornforth, John (1 of 3)., 1996, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 3)
      Note: Cornforth, John, 1937- Contains correspondence between Cornforth and William Rieder, M.M.A. Contains a book proposal entitled "English Furniture and Interiors at the Metropolitan Museum of Art" with an unpublished introduction, [Sept. 16, 1996].
    - Cornforth, John (2 of 3)., n.d. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Cornforth, John (3 of 3)., 1996, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 5)
      Note: Contains one 3 1/2 inch floppy disc labeled "John Cornforth A:\Enggal" and a copy of a manuscript on English furniture and interiors in the M.M.A. [Feb. 20, 1996?].
    - Esmerian drawings (1 of 3). (Box 63, Folder 6)
      Note: Contains 59 photographs.
    - Esmerian drawings (2 of 3). (Box 63, Folder 7)
      Note: Contains 81 photographs.
    - Esmerian drawings (3 of 3)., 1935, 1965, 1969-1970, 1973, 1976, 1980, 1988, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 8)
      Note: Contains articles and research concerning Raphael Esmerian, Filippo Pelagio Palagi and Laeken. Contains correspondence to Geoffrey de Bellagigue, a M.M.A. memorandum from John J. McKendry to John Goldsmith Phillips, correspondence to Pierre Lemoine (Musée National du Château de Versailles), Jacques Wilhelm (Musée Carnavalet) and with Carolyn J. Sargentson.
    - [Exhibitions. The Age of Neo-classicism. 1972] (Box 63, Folder 9)
      Note: Contains 7 photographs.
    - [Exhibitions. In Pursuit of Luxury: Gilt Bronze in France from Louis XIV to Napoleon. 1987.], 1985, 1987-1988, 1990, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 10)
      Note: Contains correspondence with Alan P. Darr (Detroit Institute of Arts) and Cynthia Duval (John and Mable Ringling Museum of Art). Contains drafts of preliminary checklists of objects to be considered for "In Pursuit of Luxury: Gilt Bronze in France from Louis XIV to Napoleon" (April 1987 and revised June 1987, October 1987 and June 1988) Contains 13 photographs.
    - Furniture. Glass., 1923, 1947, 1952, 1959, 1964, 1966, 1971, 1973, 1975, 1979, 1980, 1982-1993 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Furniture History Society., 1963-1964 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      Note: Furniture History Society (London, England). Contains correspondence with Geoffrey Beard (Cannon Hall Museum and Art Gallery) and Lindsay Boynton (University of Leeds). Contains Furniture History Society Yearly Newsletter no.1-3, 6-11, 14, 21-22, 30 and conference notifications.
    - Godwin, Edward William (1 of 2)., 1976, 1986-1987, 1990-1991, 1993, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 3)